Ajay	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
-LRB-	O
also	O
credited	O
as	O
Krishna	PERSON
Ajai	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
who	O
works	O
primarily	O
in	O
Kannada	ORGANIZATION
film	ORGANIZATION
industry	ORGANIZATION
Ajay	PERSON
Rao	O
debuted	O
with	O
the	O
film	O
Excuse	MISC
Me	MISC
-LRB-	O
2003	MISC
-RRB-	O
and	O
later	O
appeared	O
in	O
films	O
like	O
Taj	O
Mahal	O
-LRB-	O
2008	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Krishnan	PERSON
Love	PERSON
Story	PERSON
-LRB-	O
2010	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Krishnan	PERSON
Marriage	PERSON
Story	PERSON
-LRB-	O
2011	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
and	O
Krishna	PERSON
Leela	PERSON
-LRB-	O
2015	MISC
-RRB-	O
.	O
Ajay	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
debuted	O
with	O
the	O
film	O
Excuse	MISC
Me	MISC
-LRB-	O
2003	MISC
-RRB-	O
and	O
later	O
appeared	O
in	O
films	O
like	O
Taj	O
Mahal	O
-LRB-	O
2008	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Krishnan	PERSON
Love	PERSON
Story	PERSON
-LRB-	O
2010	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Krishnan	PERSON
Marriage	PERSON
Story	PERSON
-LRB-	O
2011	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
and	O
Krishna	PERSON
Leela	PERSON
-LRB-	O
2015	MISC
-RRB-	O
.	O
Ajaz	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actor	MISC
.	O
Khan	PERSON
was	O
a	O
wild	O
card	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
reality	O
television	O
show	O
Bigg	MISC
Boss	MISC
7	MISC
,	O
Bigg	MISC
Boss	MISC
8	MISC
,	O
where	O
he	O
finished	O
in	O
third	MISC
.	O
Ajinkya	PERSON
Dev	PERSON
is	O
also	O
the	O
executive	MISC
director	MISC
of	O
Prabhat	ORGANIZATION
Entertainment	ORGANIZATION
TV	ORGANIZATION
channel	O
Ajinkya	PERSON
Dev	PERSON
currently	O
anchoring	O
a	O
crime	O
show	O
with	O
Marathi	MISC
entertainment	O
Chanel	ORGANIZATION
.	O
Ajinkya	PERSON
working	O
with	O
Ajay	PERSON
Devgan	PERSON
in	O
his	O
Historic	O
big	O
budget	O
Movie	O
.	O
Hamid	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
-LRB-	O
27	MISC
January	MISC
1922	MISC
--	O
21	MISC
October	MISC
1998	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
better	O
known	O
by	O
his	O
stage	O
name	O
Ajit	PERSON
,	O
was	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
active	O
in	O
Hindi	MISC
films	O
Born	O
Hamid	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
,	O
near	O
the	O
historic	O
place	O
Golconda	LOCATION
,	O
Hyderabad	LOCATION
,	O
Ajit	PERSON
had	O
his	O
early	O
education	O
in	O
Warangal	LOCATION
,	O
studied	O
in	O
Govt.	ORGANIZATION
Hamid	PERSON
was	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Bashir	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Nizam	PERSON
's	O
army	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
younger	O
brother	O
,	O
Wahid	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
and	O
2	MISC
sisters	O
Film	O
director	MISC
K.	PERSON
Amarnath	PERSON
,	O
who	O
directed	O
him	O
in	O
Beqasoor	LOCATION
,	O
suggested	O
that	O
the	O
actor	MISC
change	O
his	O
long	O
name	O
of	O
Hamid	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
to	O
something	O
shorter	O
,	O
and	O
Hamid	PERSON
zeroed	O
in	O
on	O
``	O
Ajit	O
''	O
.	O
Given	O
his	O
stature	O
as	O
a	O
senior	O
artist	MISC
,	O
Ajit	PERSON
was	O
usually	O
the	O
gang	O
leader	MISC
to	O
second	MISC
tier	MISC
villains	O
-LRB-	O
such	O
as	O
Jeevan	PERSON
-LRB-	O
actor	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Prem	PERSON
Chopra	PERSON
,	O
Ranjeet	PERSON
,	O
Kader	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
and	O
Sujit	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
-RRB-	O
.	O
His	O
contemporaries	O
include	O
veteran	O
actors	O
like	O
Amrish	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
,	O
Pran	PERSON
,	O
Prem	PERSON
Chopra	PERSON
and	O
Amjad	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
.	O
Ajith	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
1	MISC
May	MISC
1971	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actor	MISC
.	O
Ajith	PERSON
was	O
the	O
middle	O
son	O
out	O
of	O
three	MISC
brothers	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
being	O
Anup	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
,	O
an	O
investor	O
,	O
and	O
Anil	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
,	O
an	O
IIT	O
Madras	LOCATION
graduate-turned-entrepreneur	O
.	O
Ajith	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
is	O
passionate	O
about	O
UAVs	MISC
and	O
drones	O
.	O
Ajmal	PERSON
Ameer	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actor	MISC
and	O
physician	MISC
who	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
and	O
Telugu	MISC
film	O
industries	O
.	O
Aju	PERSON
Varghese	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
11	MISC
January	MISC
1985	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actor	MISC
who	O
appears	O
in	O
Malayalam	MISC
cinema	O
Aju	PERSON
Varghese	PERSON
was	O
born	O
to	O
engineer	MISC
couples	O
Varghese	PERSON
P.	PERSON
K.	PERSON
and	O
Celiene	PERSON
Susan	PERSON
in	O
Thiruvalla	LOCATION
,	O
a	O
major	O
LOCATION	O
in	O
Pathanamthitta	LOCATION
Dist	LOCATION
,	O
Kerala	LOCATION
Template	O
:	O
Aju	PERSON
Varghese	PERSON
Akkineni	PERSON
Nageswara	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
-LRB-	O
20	MISC
September	MISC
1924	MISC
--	O
22	MISC
January	MISC
2014	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
widely	O
known	O
as	O
ANR	ORGANIZATION
,	O
was	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actor	MISC
and	O
producer	MISC
,	O
known	O
for	O
his	O
work	O
predominantly	O
in	O
Telugu	MISC
cinema	O
Similarly	O
,	O
Rao	PERSON
played	O
many	O
famous	O
mythological	O
figures	O
such	O
as	O
Abhimanyu	PERSON
in	O
Mayabazar	MISC
,	O
which	O
was	O
screened	O
at	O
the	O
1957	MISC
International	ORGANIZATION
Film	ORGANIZATION
Festival	ORGANIZATION
of	O
India	LOCATION
and	O
the	O
Indonesian	MISC
Film	MISC
Festival	MISC
;	O
Lord	O
Vishnu	PERSON
in	O
Chenchu	MISC
Lakshmi	MISC
;	O
Narada	PERSON
in	O
Bhookailas	MISC
;	O
Arjuna	PERSON
in	O
Sri	PERSON
Krishnarjuna	PERSON
Yuddhamu	PERSON
Akkineni	PERSON
Nageswara	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
was	O
born	O
into	O
a	O
lower	O
middle	MISC
class	MISC
family	O
on	O
20th	MISC
September	MISC
1924	MISC
in	O
Ramapuram	LOCATION
,	O
Krishna	LOCATION
District	LOCATION
,	O
Andhra	LOCATION
Pradesh	LOCATION
Akkineni	PERSON
Nageswara	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
played	O
a	O
range	O
of	O
characters	O
that	O
very	O
few	O
matched	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
Chief	MISC
Donor	MISC
and	O
President	MISC
of	O
the	O
College	O
at	O
Gudivada	LOCATION
,	O
which	O
was	O
subsequently	O
named	O
Akkineni	PERSON
Nageswara	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
College	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Alok	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
10	MISC
July	MISC
1956	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
popularly	O
known	O
as	O
Sanskaari	PERSON
Babuji	PERSON
,	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
character	O
actor	MISC
known	O
for	O
his	O
works	O
in	O
Hindi	O
cinema	O
and	O
television	O
On	O
30	MISC
December	MISC
2013	MISC
,	O
jokes	O
and	O
memes	O
based	O
on	O
characters	O
played	O
by	O
Alok	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
started	O
trending	O
on	O
social	O
media	O
and	O
spread	O
quickly	O
.	O
The	O
Curious	O
Case	O
of	O
Alok	O
Nath	MISC
-	O
Why	O
did	O
Alok	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
Trend	PERSON
on	O
Twitter	ORGANIZATION
,	O
a	O
case	O
study	O
to	O
analyse	O
the	O
content	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
buzz	O
around	O
veteran	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
actor	MISC
,	O
went	O
viral	O
on	O
4	MISC
January	MISC
2014	MISC
.	O
In	O
October	MISC
2018	MISC
,	O
amidst	O
India	LOCATION
's	O
Me	O
too	O
movement	O
,	O
Alok	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
was	O
accused	O
of	O
rape	MISC
by	O
TV	O
producer	MISC
Vinta	PERSON
Nanda	PERSON
who	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
TV	O
show	O
Tara	PERSON
in	O
the	O
mid-90s	O
.	O
.	O
Alok	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
denied	O
the	O
allegation	O
.	O
Subsequently	O
,	O
actresses	O
Renuka	PERSON
Shahane	PERSON
,	O
Himani	PERSON
Shivpuri	PERSON
,	O
Sandhya	PERSON
Mridul	PERSON
,	O
Deepika	PERSON
Amin	PERSON
,	O
and	O
an	O
anonymous	O
Hum	O
Saath-Saath	PERSON
Hain	PERSON
crew	O
member	O
have	O
either	O
admitted	O
to	O
knowing	O
about	O
Nath	PERSON
's	O
predatory	O
behaviour	O
or	O
written	O
about	O
instances	O
where	O
they	O
themselves	O
have	O
been	O
assaulted	O
by	O
him	O
On	O
15	MISC
October	MISC
2018	MISC
,	O
Nath	PERSON
sued	O
Nanda	PERSON
for	O
defamation	O
,	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
written	O
apology	O
and	O
Re	O
1	MISC
as	O
compensation	O
He	O
has	O
filed	O
the	O
case	O
jointly	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
Ashu	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
On	O
17	MISC
October	MISC
2018	MISC
,	O
Nanda	PERSON
registered	O
a	O
complaint	O
against	O
Nath	ORGANIZATION
in	O
Mumbai	ORGANIZATION
Oshiwara	ORGANIZATION
Police	ORGANIZATION
Station	ORGANIZATION
On	O
1	MISC
March	MISC
2019	MISC
,	O
Mumbai	ORGANIZATION
Mirror	ORGANIZATION
reported	O
that	O
Alok	PERSON
Nath	PERSON
is	O
all	O
set	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
role	O
of	O
a	O
judge	MISC
in	O
a	O
movie	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
Me	MISC
Too	MISC
movement	O
.	O
Amar	PERSON
Talwar	PERSON
is	O
an	O
artist	MISC
and	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
actor	MISC
.	O
Born	O
to	O
a	O
Sikh	MISC
family	O
,	O
Talwar	PERSON
was	O
educated	O
at	O
the	O
Lawrence	ORGANIZATION
School	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Sanawar	LOCATION
,	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
brother	O
Rana	PERSON
Talwar	PERSON
Before	O
becoming	O
an	O
actor	MISC
Talwar	PERSON
worked	O
as	O
a	O
photojournalist	MISC
.	O
Amjad	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
-LRB-	O
12	MISC
November	MISC
1940	MISC
--	O
27	MISC
July	MISC
1992	MISC
-RRB-	O
was	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
and	O
director	MISC
Amjad	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
Peshawar	LOCATION
,	O
British	MISC
India	LOCATION
to	O
legendary	O
actor	MISC
Jayant	PERSON
in	O
a	O
Pashtun	MISC
family	O
His	O
brothers	O
are	O
actors	O
Imtiaz	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
and	O
Inayat	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
.	O
Before	O
Amjad	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
came	O
to	O
films	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
theatre	O
actor	MISC
After	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
Sholay	O
,	O
Khan	PERSON
continued	O
to	O
play	O
negative	O
roles	O
in	O
many	O
subsequent	O
Hindi	O
films	O
in	O
the	O
1970s	MISC
,	O
1980s	MISC
and	O
early	O
1990s	MISC
--	O
superseding	O
,	O
in	O
terms	O
of	O
popularity	O
and	O
demand	O
,	O
the	O
earlier	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
,	O
Ajit	PERSON
He	O
would	O
intervene	O
and	O
negotiate	O
disputes	O
between	O
actors	O
and	O
directors/producers	O
.	O
Ahlam	PERSON
married	O
popular	O
theatre	O
actor	MISC
Zafar	PERSON
Karachiwala	PERSON
in	O
2011	MISC
.	O
Amol	PERSON
Palekar	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
24	MISC
November	MISC
1944	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
a	O
noted	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
,	O
director	MISC
and	O
producer	MISC
of	O
Hindi	O
and	O
Marathi	MISC
cinema	O
Palekar	PERSON
began	O
in	O
Marathi	MISC
experimental	O
theatre	O
with	O
Satyadev	PERSON
Dubey	PERSON
,	O
and	O
later	O
started	O
his	O
own	O
group	O
,	O
Aniket	PERSON
,	O
in	O
1972	MISC
.	O
Palekar	PERSON
made	O
his	O
debut	O
in	O
1971	MISC
with	O
the	O
Marathi	MISC
film	O
Shantata	MISC
Amol	PERSON
Palekar	PERSON
was	O
born	O
to	O
Kamlakar	PERSON
and	O
Suhasini	PERSON
Palekar	PERSON
in	O
a	O
lower-middle-class	O
family	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
.	O
Palekar	PERSON
regards	O
himself	O
as	O
an	O
agnostic	MISC
atheist	MISC
.	O
Amrishlal	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
-LRB-	O
22	MISC
June	MISC
1932	MISC
--	O
12	MISC
January	MISC
2005	MISC
-RRB-	O
was	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
important	O
figure	O
in	O
Indian	MISC
theatre	O
and	O
cinema	O
Puri	PERSON
has	O
won	O
three	MISC
Filmfare	MISC
Awards	MISC
for	O
Best	O
Supporting	O
Actor	MISC
Amrish	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
Nawanshahr	LOCATION
,	O
Punjab	LOCATION
in	O
a	O
Khatri	PERSON
family	O
of	O
Nihal	PERSON
Singh	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
and	O
Ved	PERSON
Kaur	PERSON
.	O
He	O
had	O
four	MISC
siblings	O
,	O
elder	O
brothers	O
Chaman	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
and	O
Madan	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
-LRB-	O
both	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
also	O
actors	O
-RRB-	O
,	O
elder	O
sister	O
Chandrakanta	PERSON
,	O
and	O
a	O
younger	O
brother	O
,	O
Harish	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
Amrish	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
acted	O
in	O
more	O
than	O
400	MISC
films	O
between	O
1967	MISC
and	MISC
2005	MISC
,	O
and	O
was	O
one	MISC
of	O
the	O
most	O
successful	O
villains	O
in	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
Puri	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
following	O
the	O
footsteps	O
of	O
his	O
elder	O
brothers	O
-	O
Madan	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
and	O
Chaman	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
,	O
who	O
were	O
already	O
established	O
actors	O
known	O
for	O
playing	O
villainous	O
roles	O
Puri	PERSON
went	O
on	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
Hindi	O
,	O
Kannada	MISC
,	O
Marathi	O
,	O
Hollywood	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Punjabi	MISC
,	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
Telugu	MISC
and	O
Tamil	MISC
films	O
Through	O
the	O
1970s	MISC
,	O
Puri	PERSON
often	O
worked	O
in	O
supporting	O
roles	O
,	O
usually	O
as	O
the	O
henchman	O
of	O
the	O
main	O
villain	O
.	O
In	O
1982	MISC
,	O
Puri	PERSON
played	O
the	O
main	O
villain	MISC
,	O
Jagavar	PERSON
Choudhary	PERSON
in	O
the	O
Subhash	PERSON
Ghai	PERSON
super-hit	O
film	O
Vidhaata	PERSON
Puri	O
regularly	O
featured	O
in	O
subsequent	O
Subhash	PERSON
Ghai	PERSON
films	O
Puri	PERSON
reigned	O
supreme	O
in	O
villainous	O
roles	O
in	O
the	O
1980s	MISC
and	O
1990s	MISC
.	O
In	O
those	O
decades	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
hardly	O
any	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
film	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
feature	O
Puri	PERSON
as	O
a	O
villain	O
Puri	PERSON
and	O
Spielberg	PERSON
shared	O
a	O
great	O
rapport	O
and	O
Spielberg	PERSON
often	O
said	O
in	O
interviews	O
:	O
``	O
Amrish	MISC
is	O
my	O
favorite	O
villain	O
In	O
villainous	O
roles	O
,	O
Puri	PERSON
is	O
best	O
remembered	O
as	O
``	O
Mogambo	O
'	O
in	O
Mr.	PERSON
India	PERSON
,	O
`	O
Jagavar	PERSON
''	O
in	O
Vidhaata	LOCATION
,	O
`	O
Thakral	PERSON
''	O
in	O
Meri	PERSON
Jung	PERSON
,	O
`	O
Bhujang	PERSON
'	O
in	O
Tridev	MISC
,	O
``	O
Balwant	PERSON
Rai	O
'	O
in	O
Ghayal	LOCATION
,	O
Barrister	PERSON
Chadda	PERSON
in	O
Damini	LOCATION
and	O
`	O
Thakur	PERSON
Durjan	PERSON
Singh	PERSON
''	O
in	O
Karan	PERSON
Arjun	PERSON
Since	O
the	O
1990s	MISC
until	O
his	O
death	O
in	O
2005	MISC
,	O
Puri	PERSON
also	O
featured	O
in	O
positive	O
supporting	O
roles	O
in	O
many	O
movies	O
Amrish	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
was	O
suffering	O
from	O
myelodysplastic	MISC
syndrome	MISC
,	O
a	O
rare	O
kind	O
of	O
blood	O
cancer	MISC
,	O
and	O
had	O
undergone	O
some	O
brain	O
invasive	O
surgery	MISC
for	O
his	O
condition	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
the	O
Hinduja	ORGANIZATION
hospital	ORGANIZATION
on	O
27	MISC
December	MISC
2004	MISC
.	O
Amrish	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
acted	O
in	O
more	O
than	O
400	MISC
films	O
between	O
1967	MISC
--	MISC
2005	MISC
.	O
Anant	PERSON
Nagarkatte	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
4	MISC
September	MISC
1948	MISC
-RRB-	O
known	O
as	O
Anant	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
,	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
,	O
known	O
primarily	O
for	O
his	O
work	O
in	O
Kannada	MISC
cinema	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
addition	O
he	O
appeared	O
in	O
Marathi	MISC
,	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
Telugu	MISC
and	O
Hindi	MISC
movies	O
.	O
He	O
acted	O
in	O
Malgudi	MISC
Days	MISC
,	O
directed	O
by	O
his	O
younger	O
brother	O
Shankar	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
,	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
stories	O
by	O
R.	PERSON
K.	PERSON
Narayan	PERSON
Anant	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
was	O
born	O
on	O
4	MISC
September	MISC
1948	MISC
to	O
Anandi	PERSON
and	O
Sadanand	PERSON
Nagarkatte	PERSON
in	O
the	O
Chowpatty	LOCATION
suburb	O
of	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
Nag	PERSON
had	O
his	O
early	O
schooling	O
in	O
a	O
catholic	MISC
school	O
in	O
Ajjarkad	LOCATION
,	O
Udupi	LOCATION
,	O
Ananda	PERSON
Ashrama	PERSON
in	O
Dakshina	MISC
Kannada	MISC
and	O
Chitrapur	LOCATION
Math	LOCATION
in	O
Uttara	LOCATION
Kannada	MISC
districts	O
of	O
the	O
erstwhile	O
Mysore	ORGANIZATION
State	ORGANIZATION
-LRB-	O
now	O
Karnataka	LOCATION
-RRB-	O
.	O
In	O
Karnad	PERSON
's	O
play	O
Yayati	PERSON
,	O
Nag	PERSON
played	O
the	O
role	O
of	O
Pururava	PERSON
.	O
Following	O
a	O
theatre	O
career	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
,	O
Nag	PERSON
made	O
his	O
film	O
debut	O
with	O
Sankalpa	PERSON
a	O
1973	MISC
Kannada	MISC
film	O
Anant	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
acted	O
in	O
many	O
of	O
Shyam	PERSON
Benegal	PERSON
's	O
movies	O
after	O
that	O
Although	O
he	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
for	O
his	O
mainstream	O
Kannada	MISC
films	O
,	O
Nag	PERSON
is	O
also	O
active	O
in	O
alternative	O
Indian	MISC
cinema	O
Nag	PERSON
and	O
fellow	O
popular	O
actress	MISC
Lakshmi	PERSON
are	O
a	O
hit-pair	O
in	O
Kannada	MISC
movies	O
.	O
Right	O
from	O
late	O
70	MISC
's	O
,	O
Chandanada	LOCATION
Gombe	LOCATION
,	O
Naa	PERSON
Ninna	PERSON
Bidaalare	PERSON
-LRB-	O
1979	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Benkiya	PERSON
Bale	PERSON
,	O
Ibbani	PERSON
Karagitu	PERSON
,	O
Makkaliralavva	PERSON
Mane	PERSON
Thumba	PERSON
,	O
Mududida	PERSON
Taavare	PERSON
Aralitu	PERSON
,	O
Amma	PERSON
and	O
other	O
movies	O
turned	O
out	O
as	O
blockbuster	O
hits	O
that	O
made	O
Anant	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
and	O
Lakshmi	PERSON
household	O
names	O
in	O
Karnataka	LOCATION
.	O
Beginning	O
with	O
New-Wave	MISC
artistic	O
movies	O
in	O
early	O
70	MISC
's	O
,	O
Ananth	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
branched	O
into	O
commercial	O
cinema	O
Ananth	PERSON
Nag	O
is	O
a	O
first-choice	O
not	O
just	O
to	O
old-crop	O
directors	O
but	O
also	O
young	O
directors	O
like	O
Yogaraj	PERSON
Bhat	PERSON
in	O
Mungaru	O
Male	O
,	O
Gaalipata	LOCATION
,	O
NagaShekar	O
in	O
Aramane	LOCATION
,	O
Pawan	PERSON
Wodeyar	PERSON
in	O
Googly	MISC
-LRB-	O
film	O
-RRB-	O
.	O
Nag	PERSON
acted	O
in	O
Anahat	MISC
Marathi	MISC
film	MISC
director	MISC
Amol	PERSON
Palekar	PERSON
found	O
Nag	PERSON
's	O
sensitive	O
depiction	O
of	O
the	O
king	MISC
's	O
dilemmas	O
to	O
have	O
greatly	O
enhanced	O
the	O
multifaceted	O
complexities	O
of	O
the	O
film	O
Nag	PERSON
married	O
Gayatri	PERSON
on	O
9	MISC
April	MISC
1987	MISC
.	O
Staying	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
,	O
in	O
the	O
heady	O
days	O
of	O
Socialism	MISC
,	O
Anant	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
was	O
a	O
strong	O
supporter	O
of	O
the	O
reformist	O
movement	O
.	O
Aniruddha	PERSON
Jatkar	PERSON
-LRB-	O
Anirudh	O
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
and	O
theatre	O
artist	MISC
who	O
predominantly	O
works	O
in	O
Kannada	LOCATION
Films	O
.	O
Aniruddha	PERSON
Jatkar	PERSON
is	O
currently	O
occupied	O
with	O
Documentary	O
Production	O
on	O
his	O
mother-in-law	O
Padmashree	O
Dr.	O
Bharati	PERSON
Vishnuvardhan	PERSON
Aniruddha	PERSON
Jatkar	PERSON
started	O
his	O
film	O
journey	O
through	O
2001	MISC
Dinesh	PERSON
Babu	PERSON
directorial	O
Chitte	PERSON
and	O
shot	O
to	O
fame	O
with	O
romantic-comedy	O
Tuntata	MISC
directed	O
by	O
Indrajit	PERSON
Lankesh	PERSON
Aniruddha	PERSON
Jatkar	PERSON
also	O
holds	O
four	MISC
records	O
each	O
in	O
the	O
Asia	LOCATION
book	O
of	O
records	O
and	O
India	LOCATION
book	O
of	O
records	O
for	O
his	O
directorial	O
short	O
film	O
series	O
.	O
Aniruddha	PERSON
Jatkar	PERSON
in	O
2018	MISC
released	O
most	O
number	O
of	O
short	O
films	O
in	O
all	O
of	O
Asia	LOCATION
,	O
across	O
different	O
genres	O
,	O
without	O
dialogues	O
,	O
covering	O
social	O
issues	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	MISC
.	O
Aanjjan	PERSON
Srivastav	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
2	MISC
June	MISC
1948	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
,	O
television	O
and	O
stage	O
actor	MISC
,	O
associated	O
with	O
Indian	ORGANIZATION
People	ORGANIZATION
's	ORGANIZATION
Theatre	ORGANIZATION
Association	ORGANIZATION
-LRB-	O
IPTA	ORGANIZATION
-RRB-	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
of	O
which	O
he	O
remained	O
Vice-President	MISC
for	O
several	O
years	MISC
Anjan	PERSON
Srivastav	PERSON
is	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
father	O
of	O
twins	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
and	O
a	O
girl	O
and	O
a	O
daughter	O
younger	O
to	O
the	O
twins	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
promotional	O
song	O
for	O
Kazhugu	LOCATION
alongside	O
several	O
other	O
actors	O
and	O
then	O
played	O
a	O
cameo	O
role	O
in	O
the	O
climax	O
of	O
Rajesh	PERSON
's	O
Oru	PERSON
Kal	PERSON
Oru	PERSON
Kannadi	PERSON
of	O
a	O
village	O
chieftain	O
.	O
Aarya	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
24	MISC
May	MISC
1982	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actor	MISC
who	O
appears	O
in	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
and	O
Punjabi	O
films	O
Aarya	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
started	O
his	O
film	O
career	O
with	O
Raj	PERSON
Kanwar	PERSON
's	O
Ab	PERSON
Ke	PERSON
Baras	PERSON
,	O
alongside	O
Amrita	PERSON
Rao	PERSON
.	O
Aarya	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
acted	O
in	O
the	O
Bengali	MISC
film	O
Paapi	O
in	O
2012	MISC
,	O
opposite	O
Prosanjit	O
,	O
Pooja	PERSON
Bharti	PERSON
and	O
Sayantika	PERSON
.	O
Aarya	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
released	O
his	O
first	MISC
screen	O
novel	O
My	O
fiance	O
,	O
me	O
&	O
#IFu	O
**	O
ed	O
Up	O
on	O
2	MISC
February	MISC
2015	MISC
.	O
Babbar	PERSON
won	O
the	O
National	O
Award	O
of	O
the	O
Journalist	ORGANIZATION
Association	ORGANIZATION
for	O
Upcoming	O
Actor	MISC
in	O
Action	MISC
Aarya	ORGANIZATION
Babbar	ORGANIZATION
is	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
actor	MISC
turned	O
politician	MISC
Raj	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
and	O
theatre	O
personality	O
Nadira	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
.	O
He	O
has	O
one	MISC
elder	O
sister	O
,	O
the	O
actress	MISC
Juhi	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
,	O
whose	O
husband	O
is	O
the	O
famous	O
actor	MISC
Anup	PERSON
Soni	PERSON
.	O
Aarya	PERSON
also	O
has	O
a	O
half-brother	O
,	O
the	O
actor	MISC
Prateik	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Raj	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
by	O
his	O
second	MISC
wife	O
Smita	PERSON
Patil	PERSON
.	O
Through	O
his	O
mother	O
Nadira	PERSON
Babbar	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
Nadira	PERSON
Zaheer	PERSON
-RRB-	O
,	O
Aarya	PERSON
is	O
the	O
grandson	O
of	O
the	O
communist	MISC
activist	MISC
Sajjad	PERSON
Zaheer	PERSON
and	O
first	MISC
cousin	O
of	O
Pankhuri	PERSON
Zaheer	PERSON
,	O
His	O
ex-girlfriend	O
was	O
Sristhi	PERSON
Nayyar	PERSON
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
tv	O
actor	MISC
Rajat	PERSON
Tokas	PERSON
On	O
22	MISC
Feb	MISC
2016	MISC
,	O
Aarya	PERSON
married	O
his	O
girlfriend	O
Jasmine	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
in	O
a	O
traditional	O
Sikh	MISC
wedding	O
ceremony	O
.	O
Ashish	PERSON
Vidyarthi	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
19	MISC
June	MISC
1962	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actor	MISC
and	O
motivational	O
speaker	O
,	O
known	O
for	O
his	O
work	O
in	O
11	MISC
different	O
languages	O
,	O
predominantly	O
in	O
Hindi	O
,	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
Kannada	MISC
,	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
Telugu	MISC
,	O
Bengali	MISC
,	O
English	MISC
,	O
Odia	MISC
and	O
Marathi	MISC
cinema	O
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Kannur	LOCATION
,	O
Kerala	LOCATION
,	O
India	LOCATION
to	O
Reba	PERSON
Vidyarthi	PERSON
,	O
a	O
Kathak	O
guru	MISC
and	O
Govind	PERSON
Vidyarthi	PERSON
,	O
an	O
expert	O
in	O
cataloging	O
and	O
archiving	O
vanishing	O
Performing	O
Arts	O
of	O
India	LOCATION
for	O
the	O
Sangeet	ORGANIZATION
Natak	ORGANIZATION
Akademi	ORGANIZATION
.	O
Tamil	ORGANIZATION
Cinema	ORGANIZATION
News	ORGANIZATION
-	O
Ashish	PERSON
Vidyarthi	PERSON
News	O
at	O
Maalaimalar.com	MISC
.	O
Ashok	PERSON
Saraf	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
4	MISC
June	MISC
1947	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
and	O
stage	O
actor	MISC
and	O
comedian	O
In	O
the	O
1980s	MISC
and	O
90s	MISC
,	O
Saraf	PERSON
was	O
considered	O
as	O
one	MISC
of	O
the	O
two	MISC
Marathi	MISC
comedy	O
superstars	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
actor	MISC
Laxmikant	PERSON
Berde	PERSON
.	O
Saraf	PERSON
started	O
his	O
career	O
in	O
Marathi	LOCATION
cinema	O
since	O
the	O
late	O
1960s	MISC
.	O
From	O
the	O
early	O
1980s	MISC
,	O
Saraf	PERSON
started	O
getting	O
cast	O
as	O
the	O
leading	O
hero	O
in	O
Marathi	MISC
films	O
The	O
combination	O
of	O
Ashok	PERSON
Saraf	PERSON
,	O
Laxmikant	PERSON
Berde	PERSON
,	O
Sachin	PERSON
Pilgaonkar	PERSON
and	O
Mahesh	PERSON
Kothare	PERSON
created	O
the	O
``	O
comedy	O
films	O
wave	O
''	O
in	O
Marathi	LOCATION
cinema	O
from	O
1985	MISC
that	O
lasted	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
decade	MISC
Saraf	PERSON
has	O
also	O
starred	O
in	O
television	O
serials	O
like	O
Yeh	PERSON
Choti	PERSON
Badi	PERSON
Baatein	PERSON
and	O
Hum	O
Paanch	O
-LRB-	O
as	O
Anand	PERSON
Mathur	PERSON
-RRB-	O
.	O
Ashok	PERSON
Saraf	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
Maharashtra	LOCATION
.	O
Ashok	PERSON
Saraf	PERSON
has	O
been	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
film	O
and	O
television	O
industry	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
Aamna	PERSON
Sharif	PERSON
Kapoor	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actress	MISC
who	O
appears	O
in	O
Hindi	MISC
TV	O
shows	O
and	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
films	O
After	O
dating	O
almost	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
Aamna	PERSON
Sharif	PERSON
married	O
her	O
boyfriend	O
,	O
film	O
distributor-turned-producer	O
Amit	PERSON
Kapoor	PERSON
,	O
on	O
27	MISC
December	MISC
2013	MISC
.	O
When	O
Sharif	PERSON
was	O
in	O
her	O
second	MISC
year	O
of	O
college	O
,	O
she	O
began	O
receiving	O
modelling	O
offers	O
for	O
brands	O
such	O
as	O
Close-Up	O
Toothpaste	O
,	O
Beetel	O
Mobile	MISC
phones	O
,	O
Emami	ORGANIZATION
Cosmetic	MISC
Cream	MISC
,	O
Clearasil	O
Skin	O
Cream	O
,	O
Set	O
Wet	O
,	O
Nescafe	MISC
and	O
many	O
others	O
Shariff	PERSON
made	O
her	O
acting	O
debut	O
in	O
the	O
daily	O
Kahiin	MISC
To	O
Hoga	O
where	O
she	O
played	O
the	O
protagonist	O
The	O
show	O
was	O
a	O
major	O
success	O
and	O
is	O
one	MISC
of	O
the	O
most	O
successful	O
shows	O
in	O
Star	O
Plus	O
history	O
,	O
ranking	O
#	MISC
5	MISC
on	O
Star	O
Plus	O
's	O
top	O
10	MISC
shows	O
of	O
all	O
time	MISC
Most	O
of	O
the	O
credit	O
for	O
the	O
show	O
's	O
success	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
sizzling	O
chemistry	O
between	O
Aamna	PERSON
Shariff	PERSON
and	O
her	O
co-star	O
Rajeev	PERSON
Khandelwal	PERSON
She	O
returned	O
to	O
acting	O
on	O
TV	O
after	O
six	MISC
years	MISC
,	O
playing	O
the	O
lead	O
role	O
in	O
SET	O
India	LOCATION
's	O
serial	O
``	O
Hongey	O
Judaa	O
Na	O
Hum	O
''	O
with	O
co-star	O
Raqesh	PERSON
Vashisth	PERSON
.	O
Shariff	PERSON
made	O
her	O
film	O
debut	O
in	O
the	O
2009	MISC
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
film	O
Aloo	O
Chaat	O
opposite	O
Aftab	PERSON
Shivdasani	PERSON
.	O
Aarathi	O
-LRB-	O
Kannada	MISC
:	O
????	MISC
;	O
born	O
1954	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actress	MISC
turned	O
director	MISC
who	O
works	O
predominantly	O
in	O
Kannada	MISC
language	O
films	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
lead	O
actress	MISC
in	O
more	O
than	O
125	MISC
feature	O
films	O
,	O
Aarathi	PERSON
was	O
considered	O
to	O
be	O
among	O
the	O
top	O
league	O
of	O
actresses	O
of	O
her	O
time	MISC
,	O
having	O
won	O
the	O
Filmfare	MISC
awards	O
and	O
the	O
Karnataka	LOCATION
State	O
Film	O
Award	O
for	O
Best	O
Actress	MISC
four	MISC
times	O
each	O
After	O
a	O
short	O
role	O
in	O
Gejje	PERSON
Pooje	PERSON
-LRB-	O
1969	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Aarathi	PERSON
went	O
on	O
to	O
star	O
as	O
a	O
leading	O
actress	MISC
in	O
many	O
successful	O
films	O
such	O
as	O
Naagarahaavu	O
,	O
Edakallu	PERSON
Guddada	PERSON
Mele	PERSON
,	O
Bili	PERSON
Hendthi	PERSON
,	O
Dharmasere	O
,	O
Paduvaaralli	PERSON
Pandavaru	PERSON
,	O
Ranganayaki	PERSON
,	O
Hombisilu	LOCATION
,	O
Upasane	LOCATION
,	O
Shubhamangala	LOCATION
and	O
Kaliyuga	MISC
.	O
Aarathi	ORGANIZATION
has	O
worked	O
opposite	O
all	O
the	O
leading	O
actors	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
including	O
Rajkumar	PERSON
,	O
Vishnuvardhan	PERSON
,	O
Ambareesh	O
,	O
Srinath	PERSON
,	O
Ananth	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
,	O
Shankar	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
,	O
Ashok	PERSON
,	O
Kamal	PERSON
Hassan	PERSON
,	O
Rajinikanth	PERSON
and	O
Gangadhar	PERSON
.	O
Aarathi	O
fell	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
her	O
mentor	O
and	O
director	MISC
Puttanna	PERSON
Kanagal	PERSON
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
daughter	O
Yashaswini	PERSON
in	O
1977	MISC
.	O
Aarathi	PERSON
left	O
the	O
film	O
industry	O
in	O
1987	MISC
and	O
moved	O
to	O
the	O
United	LOCATION
States	LOCATION
where	O
she	O
married	O
Chandrashekar	PERSON
Desaigoudar	PERSON
.	O
Aarthi	PERSON
Agarwal	PERSON
-LRB-	O
March	MISC
5	MISC
,	MISC
1984	MISC
--	O
June	MISC
6	MISC
,	MISC
2015	MISC
-RRB-	O
was	O
an	O
Indian-American	MISC
actress	MISC
who	O
primarily	O
worked	O
in	O
Telugu	MISC
cinema	O
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
Tollywood	ORGANIZATION
.	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
older	O
sister	O
of	O
Aditi	PERSON
Agarwal	PERSON
,	O
also	O
an	O
actress	MISC
Agarwal	O
nandini	O
was	O
born	O
on	O
March	MISC
5	MISC
,	MISC
1984	MISC
in	O
New	LOCATION
Jersey	LOCATION
to	O
Gujarati	MISC
parents	MISC
Agarwal	O
made	O
her	O
Telugu	MISC
film	O
debut	O
in	O
Nuvvu	MISC
Naaku	MISC
Nachav	MISC
with	O
actor	MISC
Venkatesh	PERSON
.	O
In	O
2005	MISC
,	O
The	O
Hindu	MISC
reported	O
that	O
Agarwal	PERSON
had	O
attempted	O
suicide	MISC
after	O
she	O
was	O
hospitalized	O
with	O
internal	O
head	O
injuries	O
at	O
Apollo	ORGANIZATION
Hospital	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Jubilee	LOCATION
Hills	LOCATION
,	O
Hyderabad	LOCATION
and	O
put	O
on	O
ventilator	MISC
support	O
.	O
In	O
2007	MISC
,	O
Agarwal	PERSON
married	O
Tasval	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
,	O
a	O
U.S.based	MISC
Indian	MISC
software	MISC
engineer	MISC
;	O
the	O
couple	O
divorced	O
in	O
2009	MISC
.	O
On	O
June	MISC
6	MISC
,	MISC
2015	MISC
,	O
Agarwal	PERSON
was	O
pronounced	O
dead	O
on	O
arrival	O
at	O
AtlantiCare	ORGANIZATION
Regional	ORGANIZATION
Medical	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
in	O
Atlantic	LOCATION
LOCATION	LOCATION
,	O
New	LOCATION
Jersey	LOCATION
.	O
Agarwal	PERSON
,	O
who	O
had	O
undergone	O
a	O
liposuction	O
surgery	MISC
six	MISC
weeks	MISC
prior	O
,	O
had	O
severe	O
breathing	O
problems	O
before	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
Abhirami	PERSON
-LRB-	O
pronunciation	O
-LRB-	O
help	O
	O
info	O
born	O
Divya	PERSON
Gopikumar	PERSON
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actress	MISC
and	O
television	O
host	MISC
.	O
Besides	O
Tamil	MISC
and	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
she	O
has	O
appeared	O
in	O
Telugu	MISC
and	O
Kannada	MISC
films	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
notable	O
Tollywood	ORGANIZATION
actress	MISC
.	O
Adah	PERSON
Sharma	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
who	O
mainly	O
appears	O
in	O
Hindi	O
and	O
Telugu	MISC
language	O
films	O
Sharma	PERSON
,	O
after	O
finishing	O
her	O
schooling	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
acting	O
debut	O
with	O
a	O
leading	O
role	O
in	O
the	O
2008	MISC
Hindi	MISC
language	O
horror	O
film	O
1920	MISC
,	O
a	O
box	O
office	O
success	O
Adah	PERSON
Sharma	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
a	O
Tamil	MISC
Brahmin	MISC
family	O
and	O
was	O
raised	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
,	O
Maharashtra	LOCATION
.	O
Her	O
father	O
S.	PERSON
L.	PERSON
Sharma	PERSON
,	O
who	O
hails	O
from	O
Madurai	LOCATION
,	O
Tamil	LOCATION
Nadu	LOCATION
,	O
was	O
a	O
captain	MISC
in	O
the	O
merchant	MISC
navy	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
a	O
native	O
from	O
Nattupura	LOCATION
-LRB-	O
bordering	O
Palakkad	LOCATION
-RRB-	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
classical	O
dancer	MISC
.	O
Sharma	PERSON
is	O
a	O
gymnast	MISC
.	O
Trying	O
to	O
enter	O
in	O
the	O
film	O
industry	O
,	O
Sharma	PERSON
auditioned	O
for	O
several	O
roles	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
,	O
but	O
was	O
rejected	O
either	O
because	O
of	O
her	O
curly	O
hair	O
or	O
because	O
the	O
makers	O
felt	O
that	O
she	O
looked	O
too	O
young	O
.	O
The	O
film	O
was	O
a	O
commercial	O
success	O
,	O
too	O
,	O
Bhatt	PERSON
's	O
first	MISC
box	O
office	O
hit	O
after	O
six	MISC
years	MISC
and	O
10	MISC
films	O
,	O
and	O
earned	O
Sharma	PERSON
a	O
Best	O
Female	O
Debut	O
nomination	O
at	O
the	O
54th	MISC
Filmfare	ORGANIZATION
Awards	ORGANIZATION
Phhir	MISC
,	O
however	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
well	O
received	O
as	O
1920	MISC
,	O
opening	O
to	O
negative	O
reviews	O
,	O
and	O
failing	O
at	O
the	O
box	O
office	O
,	O
with	O
Sharma	PERSON
getting	O
mixed	O
response	O
for	O
her	O
performance	O
.	O
In	O
2014	MISC
,	O
Sharma	PERSON
had	O
two	MISC
releases	O
:	O
Puri	PERSON
Jagannadh	PERSON
's	O
romance	O
Heart	MISC
Attack	MISC
opposite	O
Nithiin	PERSON
,	O
that	O
marked	O
her	O
Telugu	MISC
debut	O
and	O
a	O
Hindi	MISC
film	O
Hasee	PERSON
Toh	PERSON
Phasee	PERSON
alongside	O
Sidharth	PERSON
Malhotra	PERSON
and	O
Parineeti	ORGANIZATION
Chopra	ORGANIZATION
,	O
which	O
released	O
seven	MISC
days	MISC
later	O
and	O
featured	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
supporting	O
role	O
.	O
Sharma	PERSON
received	O
positive	O
remarks	O
for	O
her	O
performance	O
in	O
Heart	MISC
Attack	MISC
,	O
with	O
The	ORGANIZATION
Times	ORGANIZATION
of	ORGANIZATION
India	ORGANIZATION
writing	O
that	O
she	O
``	O
looks	O
like	O
a	O
natural	O
actress	MISC
and	O
does	O
a	O
decent	O
job	O
''	O
while	O
telugu.com	MISC
felt	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
``	O
stunning	O
debut	O
''	O
.	O
Directed	O
by	O
Harish	PERSON
Shankar	PERSON
,	O
the	O
film	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
moderate	O
success	O
,	O
and	O
Sharma	PERSON
received	O
good	O
reviews	O
for	O
her	O
performance	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
5th	MISC
edition	O
of	O
Indian	ORGANIZATION
Federation	ORGANIZATION
for	ORGANIZATION
Fashion	ORGANIZATION
Development	ORGANIZATION
's	ORGANIZATION
India	ORGANIZATION
Runway	ORGANIZATION
Week	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Sharma	PERSON
dazzled	O
in	O
a	O
beautiful	O
lehenga	O
as	O
she	O
walked	O
the	O
ramp	O
for	O
Shravan	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
Sharma	PERSON
had	O
three	MISC
releases	O
in	O
February	MISC
2016	MISC
,	O
two	MISC
of	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
Telugu	MISC
language	O
.	O
Aditi	PERSON
Govitrikar	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
14	MISC
May	MISC
1972	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
model	MISC
,	O
actress	MISC
and	O
a	O
doctor	MISC
.	O
From	O
1997	MISC
until	MISC
2004	MISC
,	O
Dr.	O
Govitrikar	PERSON
remains	O
the	O
only	O
Indian	MISC
supermodel	MISC
with	O
the	O
both	O
medical	O
doctor	MISC
and	O
psychologist	MISC
qualification	O
Dr	O
.	O
Govitrikar	PERSON
remains	O
the	O
first	MISC
and	O
the	O
only	O
Indian	MISC
woman	O
to	O
have	O
won	O
the	O
Mrs.	O
World	O
MISC	MISC
Dr	O
.	O
Govitrikar	PERSON
ventured	O
into	O
acting	O
when	O
she	O
played	O
the	O
lead	O
role	O
in	O
Thammudu	LOCATION
-LRB-	O
1999	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
a	O
movie	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
runaway	O
hit	O
Dr	O
.	O
Govitrikar	PERSON
launched	O
PETA	ORGANIZATION
in	O
India	LOCATION
and	O
has	O
also	O
endorsed	O
top	O
tier	MISC
international	O
brands	O
such	O
as	O
Coca	ORGANIZATION
Cola	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Chopard	PERSON
,	O
Fendi	PERSON
and	O
Harry	PERSON
Winston	PERSON
.	O
Since	PERSON
winning	O
Mrs.	O
World	O
2001	MISC
,	O
Govitrikar	PERSON
continued	O
modeling	O
and	O
also	O
appeared	O
in	O
minor	O
roles	O
in	O
a	O
MISC	O
of	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
and	O
South	MISC
Indian	MISC
films	O
.	O
Govitrikar	O
has	O
a	O
younger	O
sister	O
,	O
Arzoo	PERSON
Govitrikar	PERSON
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
electronics	O
engineer-turned-actress	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
show	O
Kalakarz	PERSON
as	O
being	O
the	O
judge	MISC
she	O
did	O
n't	O
like	O
the	O
judgments	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
Richa	PERSON
Tiwari	PERSON
from	O
Sagar	LOCATION
,	O
Madhya	LOCATION
Pradesh	LOCATION
to	O
win	O
which	O
later	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
final	O
round	O
by	O
Govitrikar	PERSON
's	O
judgement	O
.	O
Aditi	PERSON
Sarangdhar	PERSON
is	O
a	O
Marathi	MISC
actress	MISC
Aditi	PERSON
was	O
born	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Dipak	PERSON
and	O
Shaila	PERSON
Sarangdhar	PERSON
,	O
a	O
middle-class	MISC
family	O
from	O
Kalyan	LOCATION
She	O
also	O
acted	O
in	O
Female	O
version	O
of	O
Devendra	PERSON
Pem	PERSON
's	O
`	O
All	O
The	O
Best	O
'	O
and	O
then	O
Zee	O
Marathi	O
's	O
`	O
Vadalvat	O
'	O
happens	O
and	O
Aditi	PERSON
Sarangdhar	PERSON
becomes	O
household	O
name	O
in	O
Maharashtra	LOCATION
.	O
Aditi	PERSON
Sharma	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
24	MISC
August	MISC
1983	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actress	MISC
who	O
appears	O
in	O
films	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
television	O
shows	O
Sharma	PERSON
is	O
the	O
winner	O
of	O
talent-hunt	O
show	O
India	LOCATION
's	O
Best	O
Cinestars	O
Ki	O
Khoj	O
that	O
premiered	O
on	O
Zee	ORGANIZATION
TV	ORGANIZATION
in	O
2004	MISC
.	O
From	O
2015	MISC
to	MISC
2017	MISC
,	O
Sharma	PERSON
portrayed	O
Gangaa	PERSON
Shukla	PERSON
as	O
lawyer	MISC
in	O
&	O
TV	O
's	O
Gangaa	LOCATION
opposite	O
Vishal	PERSON
Vashishtha	PERSON
and	O
Shakti	PERSON
Anand	PERSON
.	O
Ahaana	PERSON
Krishna	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
13	MISC
October	MISC
1995	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
and	O
model	MISC
who	O
appears	O
in	O
Malayalam	MISC
films	O
.	O
Ahaana	O
was	O
born	O
as	O
the	O
eldest	O
of	O
the	O
four	MISC
daughters	O
of	O
actor	MISC
KrishnaKumar	PERSON
and	O
his	O
wife	O
Sindhu	PERSON
.	O
Aindrita	PERSON
Ray	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
,	O
primarily	O
appearing	O
in	O
Kannada	MISC
films	O
Aindrita	PERSON
Ray	PERSON
was	O
born	O
as	O
the	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
into	O
a	O
Bengali	MISC
family	O
in	O
Udaipur	LOCATION
,	O
Rajasthan	LOCATION
,	O
where	O
she	O
spent	O
her	O
childhood	O
,	O
before	O
moving	O
to	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
.	O
With	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
A.	PERSON
K.	PERSON
Ray	PERSON
,	O
being	O
a	O
prosthodontist	MISC
in	O
the	O
Indian	ORGANIZATION
Air	ORGANIZATION
Force	ORGANIZATION
,	O
she	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
family	O
moved	O
from	O
one	MISC
place	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
finally	O
settling	O
in	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
.	O
Ray	PERSON
studied	O
at	O
Baldwin	ORGANIZATION
Girls	ORGANIZATION
High	ORGANIZATION
School	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
.	O
Aindrita	PERSON
Ray	PERSON
trained	O
under	O
fashion	O
choreographer	MISC
M.	PERSON
S.	PERSON
Sreedhar	PERSON
.	O
Aindrita	PERSON
Ray	PERSON
began	O
her	O
acting	O
career	O
in	O
the	O
2008	MISC
film	O
Meravanige	LOCATION
,	O
playing	O
the	O
role	O
of	O
Nandini	MISC
,	O
the	O
love	O
interest	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
actor	MISC
played	O
by	O
Prajwal	PERSON
Devaraj	PERSON
In	O
2009	MISC
,	O
Ray	PERSON
appeared	O
in	O
Vaayuputra	LOCATION
,	O
an	O
action	O
movie	O
,	O
alongside	O
the	O
debutant	O
Chiranjeevi	PERSON
Sarja	PERSON
.	O
After	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
flops	O
,	O
Ray	PERSON
was	O
cast	O
in	O
the	O
supporting	O
role	O
in	O
the	O
Puneeth	PERSON
Rajkumar	PERSON
starrer	O
Paramathma	PERSON
Ray	PERSON
will	O
appear	O
in	O
Raja	PERSON
Chanda	PERSON
's	O
Bengali	MISC
film	O
Amar	PERSON
Apanjan	PERSON
,	O
alongside	O
Soham	PERSON
Chakraborty	PERSON
,	O
Priyanka	PERSON
Sarkar	PERSON
and	O
Subhasree	PERSON
.	O
Aishwariya	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actress	MISC
who	O
has	O
acted	O
in	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
and	O
Telugu	MISC
movies	O
along	O
with	O
several	O
Malayalam	MISC
television	O
serials	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
popular	O
actress	MISC
Lakshmi	PERSON
.	O
She	O
then	O
accepted	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
television	O
show	O
produced	O
by	O
Suresh	PERSON
Chandra	PERSON
Menon	PERSON
,	O
after	O
being	O
convinced	O
by	O
her	O
friend	O
,	O
actress	MISC
Revathi	PERSON
.	O
Born	O
as	O
Shanta	PERSON
Meena	PERSON
Bhaskar	PERSON
,	O
to	O
Tamil	MISC
father	O
K	PERSON
Bhaskaran	PERSON
and	O
half	O
Tamil	MISC
and	O
Telugu	MISC
actress	MISC
Lakshmi	PERSON
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
half-sister	O
from	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
third	MISC
marriage	O
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Arjun	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Arjun	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
,	O
Karnataka	LOCATION
and	O
is	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
popular	O
film	O
actor	MISC
and	O
director	MISC
Arjun	PERSON
Sarja	PERSON
and	O
former	O
actress	MISC
Asharani	PERSON
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Devan	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
and	O
Beauty	O
queen	MISC
from	O
Kerala	LOCATION
who	O
has	O
acted	O
in	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
Tamil	MISC
and	O
Kannada	MISC
Language	O
films	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
was	O
born	O
to	O
S.	PERSON
Devan	PERSON
,	O
who	O
is	O
from	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
,	O
and	O
Sheeja	PERSON
Devan	PERSON
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
and	O
a	O
model	MISC
,	O
who	O
has	O
appeared	O
in	O
South	MISC
Indian	MISC
films	O
,	O
primarily	O
in	O
Kannada	MISC
cinema	O
.	O
Nag	PERSON
debuted	O
as	O
a	O
lead	O
actress	MISC
in	O
the	O
2008	MISC
released	O
film	O
Neene	MISC
Neene	MISC
opposite	O
Dhyan	PERSON
and	O
Ananth	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
when	O
she	O
was	O
16	MISC
years	MISC
old	O
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
got	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
praise	O
for	O
holding	O
her	O
own	O
against	O
Anant	PERSON
Nag	PERSON
who	O
played	O
her	O
dad	O
in	O
the	O
film	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
brief	O
hiatus	O
,	O
Nag	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
comedy	O
,	O
Kal	PERSON
Manja	PERSON
,	O
which	O
also	O
had	O
Komal	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
in	O
the	O
cast	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
playing	O
the	O
lead	O
protagonist	O
role	O
in	O
T.	PERSON
S.	PERSON
Nagabharana	PERSON
's	O
next	O
directional	O
Vasundhara	PERSON
.	O
Nag	O
is	O
playing	O
a	O
lead	O
role	O
in	O
the	O
movie	O
Muddu	PERSON
Manase	PERSON
where	O
she	O
is	O
seen	O
riding	O
a	O
Royal	ORGANIZATION
Enfield	ORGANIZATION
with	O
ease	O
.	O
Nag	PERSON
played	O
a	O
media	O
reporter	MISC
in	O
the	O
movie	O
Jaathre	O
in	O
2015	MISC
.	O
Nag	O
is	O
currently	O
shooting	O
for	O
her	O
next	O
movie	O
``	O
The	O
Gulaabi	O
street	O
''	O
and	O
is	O
playing	O
a	O
lead	O
role	O
in	O
the	O
movie	O
which	O
is	O
vaguely	O
inspired	O
by	O
the	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
movie	O
Fashion	O
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Rajesh	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
,	O
who	O
has	O
appeared	O
in	O
leading	O
roles	O
primarily	O
in	O
Tamil	MISC
cinema	O
.	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
's	O
father	O
Rajesh	PERSON
was	O
also	O
an	O
actor	MISC
who	O
had	O
appeared	O
in	O
54	MISC
films	O
in	O
Telugu	MISC
.	O
Baradwaj	PERSON
Rangan	PERSON
wrote	O
,	O
``	O
it	O
features	O
stunning	O
performances	O
from	O
everyone	O
...	O
especially	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Rajesh	PERSON
,	O
who	O
plays	O
the	O
kids	O
'	O
mother	O
with	O
a	O
world-weariness	O
that	O
belies	O
her	O
years	O
''	O
.	O
Based	O
on	O
her	O
performance	O
in	O
Kaakka	LOCATION
Muttai	LOCATION
,	O
Arjun	PERSON
Rampal	PERSON
selected	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Rajesh	PERSON
in	O
the	O
challenging	O
role	O
of	O
Asha	PERSON
Gawli	PERSON
for	O
the	O
film	O
Daddy	O
2018	MISC
was	O
the	O
most	O
successful	O
year	O
for	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Rajesh	PERSON
as	O
she	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
big	O
hits	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
Akanksha	PERSON
Juneja	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
television	O
actress	MISC
.	O
Juneja	O
started	O
her	O
television	O
career	O
with	O
STAR	O
Plus	O
's	O
Mahayatra	MISC
.	O
Besides	O
her	O
television	O
work	O
,	O
Akanksha	PERSON
Juneja	PERSON
has	O
also	O
worked	O
in	O
some	O
films	O
.	O
Akanksha	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
is	O
Indian	MISC
model	MISC
,	O
and	O
film	O
actress	MISC
,	O
known	O
for	O
her	O
works	O
in	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
and	O
Bollywood	ORGANIZATION
Akanksha	PERSON
Puri	PERSON
hails	O
from	O
Madhya	LOCATION
Pradesh	LOCATION
and	O
has	O
done	O
her	O
schooling	O
from	O
a	O
convent	O
in	O
Bhopal	LOCATION
.	O
Aksha	PERSON
Pardasany	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
actress	MISC
.	O
Akshara	PERSON
Gowda	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
Harini	PERSON
Gowda	PERSON
on	O
24	MISC
December	MISC
1991	MISC
in	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
,	O
Karnataka	LOCATION
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
who	O
has	O
appeared	O
in	O
Hindi	MISC
and	O
Tamil	MISC
films	O
.	O
Gowda	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
,	O
Karnataka	LOCATION
to	O
father	O
,	O
the	O
businessman	MISC
JPS	PERSON
Gowda	PERSON
,	O
and	O
Gowri	PERSON
Gowda	PERSON
.	O
Gowda	PERSON
attended	O
the	O
New	ORGANIZATION
Cambridge	ORGANIZATION
High	ORGANIZATION
School	ORGANIZATION
in	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
,	O
and	O
then	O
completed	O
her	O
pre-university	O
studies	O
at	O
Vijaya	ORGANIZATION
Junior	ORGANIZATION
College	ORGANIZATION
,	O
before	O
going	O
on	O
to	O
graduate	O
from	O
Engineering	O
in	O
SKIT	ORGANIZATION
college	ORGANIZATION
,	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
In	O
April	MISC
2011	MISC
,	O
Akshara	PERSON
Gowda	PERSON
was	O
linked	O
to	O
Indian	MISC
cricketer	MISC
Yuvraj	PERSON
Singh	PERSON
.	O
However	O
,	O
Gowda	PERSON
immediately	O
denied	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mere	O
media	O
imagination	O
In	O
a	O
2017	MISC
interview	O
,	O
Gowda	PERSON
spoke	O
about	O
her	O
personal	O
experience	O
of	O
overcoming	O
depression	O
.	O
Akshara	PERSON
Haasan	PERSON
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
who	O
has	O
appeared	O
in	O
Hindi	O
and	O
Tamil	MISC
language	O
films	O
The	O
daughter	O
of	O
actors	O
Kamal	PERSON
Haasan	PERSON
and	O
Sarika	PERSON
Thakur	PERSON
,	O
and	O
the	O
younger	O
sister	O
of	O
Shruti	PERSON
Haasan	PERSON
,	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
film	O
debut	O
with	O
the	O
comedy	O
drama	O
Shamitabh	O
-LRB-	O
2015	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
and	O
later	O
appeared	O
in	O
Vivegam	LOCATION
-LRB-	O
2017	MISC
-RRB-	O
.	O
Akshara	PERSON
Haasan	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
Chennai	LOCATION
,	O
Tamil	LOCATION
Nadu	LOCATION
to	O
actors	O
Kamal	PERSON
Haasan	PERSON
and	O
Sarika	PERSON
Thakur	PERSON
.	O
Shruti	PERSON
Haasan	PERSON
is	O
her	O
elder	O
sister	O
Akshara	O
Haasan	O
lives	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
with	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
Haasan	PERSON
has	O
worked	O
as	O
an	O
assistant	MISC
director	MISC
to	O
Rahul	PERSON
Dholakia	PERSON
on	O
the	O
2010	MISC
film	O
Society	O
,	O
starring	O
her	O
mother	O
Sarika	PERSON
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Ram	PERSON
Moorthy	PERSON
,	O
Uzer	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
,	O
E.	PERSON
Niwas	PERSON
and	O
Ruchi	PERSON
Narain	PERSON
on	O
my	O
many	O
AD	O
films	O
in	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
Haasan	PERSON
made	O
her	O
debut	O
as	O
an	O
actress	MISC
in	O
Shamitabh	LOCATION
,	O
opposite	O
Dhanush	O
,	O
which	O
also	O
has	O
Amitabh	ORGANIZATION
Bachchan	ORGANIZATION
in	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
co-actor	O
of	O
Ajith	PERSON
Kumar	PERSON
in	O
Vivegam	LOCATION
in	O
Tamil	MISC
.	O
Iswarya	PERSON
Menon	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
Aishwarya	PERSON
Menon	PERSON
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
who	O
acts	O
in	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
Kannada	MISC
and	O
Malayalam	MISC
films	O
Iswarya	PERSON
Menon	PERSON
was	O
born	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
Erode	LOCATION
,	O
Tamil	MISC
Nadu	LOCATION
Iswarya	PERSON
Menon	PERSON
made	O
her	O
next	O
Malayalam	MISC
debut	O
in	O
the	O
romance	O
film	O
Monsoon	O
Mangoes	O
co-starring	O
Fahadh	PERSON
Faasil	PERSON
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
portrays	O
Rekha	PERSON
,	O
a	O
``	O
practical	O
and	O
independent	MISC
young	O
woman	O
''	O
.	O
Amala	PERSON
Akkineni	PERSON
-LRB-	O
ne	O
Mukherjee	PERSON
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
,	O
Bharata	O
Natyam	O
dancer	MISC
,	O
and	O
an	O
animal	MISC
welfare	MISC
activist	MISC
.	O
She	O
received	O
a	O
CineMAA	O
Award	O
for	O
Best	O
Outstanding	O
Actress	MISC
and	O
Telugu	MISC
category	O
Filmfare	O
Award	O
for	O
best	O
supporting	O
actress	MISC
in	O
2013	MISC
for	O
her	O
portrayal	O
.	O
Amala	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
26	MISC
October	MISC
1991	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
who	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
South	MISC
Indian	MISC
Film	O
Industry	ORGANIZATION
.	O
About	O
the	O
Tamil	MISC
version	O
,	O
a	O
reviewer	MISC
from	O
The	O
Hindu	MISC
wrote	O
:	O
``	O
Amala	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
,	O
after	O
coming	O
across	O
as	O
convincing	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
few	O
movies	O
,	O
looks	O
finally	O
set	O
as	O
a	O
leading	O
lady	O
''	O
,	O
while	O
another	O
critic	MISC
labelled	O
that	O
she	O
``	O
comes	O
across	O
as	O
natural	O
''	O
and	O
``	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pleasure	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
role	O
and	O
costumes	O
that	O
suit	O
her	O
age	O
as	O
compared	O
to	O
her	O
recent	O
movies	O
''	O
.	O
Sangeetha	PERSON
Devi	PERSON
Dundroo	PERSON
of	O
The	O
Hindu	MISC
commented	O
:	O
``	O
Amala	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
manages	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
a	O
character	O
that	O
traverses	O
a	O
thin	O
line	O
between	O
being	O
naive	O
and	O
downright	O
silly	O
.	O
''	O
Another	O
reviewer	MISC
,	O
Sasidhar	PERSON
AS	O
from	O
The	ORGANIZATION
Times	ORGANIZATION
of	ORGANIZATION
India	ORGANIZATION
commented	O
:	O
``	O
Amala	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
's	O
characterisation	O
is	O
a	O
delight	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
plays	O
Komali	PERSON
so	O
effectively	O
that	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
left	O
wondering	O
who	O
else	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
role	O
better	O
than	O
her	O
Amala	PERSON
was	O
born	O
in	O
a	O
Christian	MISC
family	O
at	O
Ernakulam	LOCATION
,	O
Kerala	LOCATION
to	O
Paul	PERSON
Varghese	PERSON
and	O
Annice	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
.	O
Her	O
brother	O
Abijith	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
also	O
appeared	O
in	O
films	O
following	O
Amala	PERSON
's	O
entry	O
into	O
the	O
film	O
industry	O
.	O
Her	O
father	O
had	O
been	O
strictly	O
against	O
Amala	PERSON
pursuing	O
an	O
acting	O
career	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
accept	O
her	O
decision	O
with	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
Abijith	PERSON
Paul	PERSON
,	O
strongly	O
backing	O
her	O
ambition	O
.	O
Ambika	PERSON
-LRB-	O
born	O
24	MISC
August	MISC
1962	MISC
-RRB-	O
is	O
an	O
Indian	MISC
film	O
actress	MISC
known	O
for	O
her	O
works	O
predominantly	O
in	O
Tamil	MISC
,	O
Malayalam	MISC
and	O
Kannada	MISC
films	O
Her	O
younger	O
sister	O
Radha	PERSON
,	O
was	O
also	O
an	O
actress	MISC
But	O
with	O
films	O
such	O
as	O
Neelathaamara	O
-LRB-	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
again	O
in	O
2009	MISC
-RRB-	O
and	O
Lejjavathi	PERSON
,	O
she	O
became	O
a	O
busy	O
actress	MISC
within	O
a	O
few	O
years	O
not	O
only	O
in	O
Malayalam	MISC
,	O
but	O
also	O
in	O
Tamil	MISC
and	O
Kannada	MISC
In	O
the	O
zenith	O
of	O
her	O
career	O
she	O
was	O
paired	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
movie	O
with	O
her	O
sister	O
Radha	PERSON
in	O
Kadhal	LOCATION
Parisu	LOCATION
,	O
where	O
both	O
actresses	O
demonstrated	O
their	O
acting	O
prowess	O
by	O
taking	O
on	O
roles	O
of	O
two	MISC
young	O
,	O
beautiful	O
sisters	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
strong	O
,	O
yet	O
conflicting	O
personalities	O
.	O
Achhnera	LOCATION
,	O
-LRB-	O
alternate	O
spelling	O
:	O
Achnera	LOCATION
-RRB-	O
is	O
a	O
town	O
and	O
a	O
municipal	O
board	O
in	O
Agra	LOCATION
district	O
in	O
the	O
Indian	MISC
state	O
of	O
Uttar	LOCATION
Pradesh	LOCATION
.	O
Achhnera	LOCATION
is	O
located	O
at	O
27	MISC
	MISC
11	MISC
?	O
N	O
77	MISC
	O
46	MISC
?	MISC
E	O
/	O
27.18	MISC
	MISC
N	O
77.77	MISC
	MISC
E	O
/	O
27.18	MISC
;	O
77.77	MISC
.	O
Achhnera	LOCATION
comes	O
under	O
Tehsil	O
Kiraoli	LOCATION
The	O
temperature	O
in	O
Achhnera	LOCATION
is	O
typical	O
of	O
northern	O
India	LOCATION
,	O
with	O
cold	O
nights	O
in	O
winter	MISC
and	O
heat	O
waves	O
in	O
summer	O
As	O
of	O
2011	MISC
India	LOCATION
census	O
,	O
Achhnera	PERSON
had	O
a	O
population	O
of	O
30045	MISC
.	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
is	O
located	O
at	O
23	MISC
	MISC
10	MISC
?	O
N	O
72	MISC
	O
35	MISC
?	MISC
E	O
/	O
23.17	MISC
	MISC
N	O
72.58	MISC
	MISC
E	O
/	O
23.17	MISC
;	O
72.58	MISC
.	O
As	O
of	O
2001	MISC
India	LOCATION
census	O
,	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
had	O
a	O
population	O
of	O
9774	MISC
.	O
The	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
Stepwell	LOCATION
is	O
a	O
popular	O
tourist	O
attraction	O
of	O
the	O
LOCATION	O
and	O
is	O
situated	O
18	MISC
kilometres	O
-LRB-	O
11	MISC
mi	O
-RRB-	O
away	O
from	O
Ghandhinagar	LOCATION
An	O
expansive	O
non-sectarian	MISC
Trimandir	ORGANIZATION
inspired	O
by	O
Dada	PERSON
Bhagwan	PERSON
opened	O
December	MISC
29	MISC
,	MISC
2002	MISC
at	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
-LRB-	O
near	O
Ahmedabad-Kalol	LOCATION
Highway	LOCATION
-RRB-	O
on	O
the	O
outskirts	O
of	O
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
.	O
The	O
left	O
sanctum	O
of	O
the	O
Trimandir	ORGANIZATION
Simandhar	ORGANIZATION
Swami	ORGANIZATION
at	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
Trimandir	LOCATION
hosts	O
Shivling	MISC
,	O
Parvati	PERSON
Devi	PERSON
,	O
Hanumanji	PERSON
and	O
Ganapatiji	LOCATION
whereas	O
the	O
right	O
sanctum	O
comprises	O
Krishna	PERSON
Bhagwan	PERSON
,	O
Tirupati	PERSON
Balaji	PERSON
Shreenathji	PERSON
,	O
Bhadrakali	PERSON
Mataji	PERSON
and	O
Amba	O
Mata	MISC
.	O
Besides	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
,	O
similar	O
Trimandirs	MISC
of	O
varying	O
sizes	O
have	O
cropped	O
up	O
at	O
Rajkot	O
-LRB-	O
January	MISC
2006	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Bhuj	LOCATION
-LRB-	O
December	MISC
2009	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
Godhra	LOCATION
-LRB-	O
January	MISC
2012	MISC
-RRB-	O
,	O
and	O
various	O
other	O
locations	O
Jagannath	LOCATION
Temple	O
-LRB-	O
JCARC	LOCATION
Campus	LOCATION
-RRB-	O
,	O
Gandhinagar	LOCATION
is	O
located	O
close	O
to	O
cloverleaf	O
junction	O
of	O
Adalaj	O
,	O
northerly	O
to	O
Trimandir	MISC
Popular	O
temple	O
of	O
Lord	O
Hanuman	PERSON
at	O
Jamiyatpura	LOCATION
,	O
Adalaj	LOCATION
is	O
located	O
Northwesterly	O
to	O
Trimandir	LOCATION
,	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
kilometer	O
far	O
.	O
Adra	LOCATION
is	O
an	O
important	O
census	O
town	O
and	O
a	O
railway	O
colony	O
which	O
was	O
originally	O
known	O
for	O
its	O
90	MISC
%	MISC
of	O
Anglo	MISC
Indian	MISC
population	O
in	O
Purulia	LOCATION
district	O
in	O
the	O
Indian	MISC
state	O
of	O
West	LOCATION
Bengal	LOCATION
This	O
town	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
as	O
a	O
cultural	O
hub	O
in	O
Purulia	LOCATION
district	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
populated	O
area	O
.	O
As	O
per	O
administration	O
,	O
Northern	O
part	O
falls	O
under	O
Raghunathpur	LOCATION
block	O
area	O
of	O
Bankura	LOCATION
Lok	LOCATION
Sabha	LOCATION
constituency	O
and	O
Southern	MISC
part	O
falls	O
under	O
Kashipur	LOCATION
block	O
area	O
of	O
Purulia	LOCATION
Lok	LOCATION
Sabha	LOCATION
constituency	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
the	O
headquarters	O
of	O
the	O
Afzalpur	MISC
taluk	MISC
.	O
Afzalpur	O
is	O
located	O
at	O
17	MISC
	MISC
12	MISC
?	O
N	O
76	MISC
	O
21	MISC
?	MISC
E	O
/	O
17.2	MISC
	MISC
N	O
76.35	MISC
	MISC
E	O
/	O
17.2	MISC
;	O
76.35	MISC
.	O
